傲骨之战
第一季 第九集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译      Alex  秋乙一  Margaery  吃冰棒
翻译      dzysteven  capitaljack  一点都不酷喵
校对      free维塔  某羽
时间轴      Avis  西·查  映映
后期      你是不是饿得慌
总监      free维塔
公告     人人影视永久官方网站 www.YYeTs.com
最后一刻有什么忠告吗
Any last-minute advice?
没有
Nope.
实话实说就好
Just tell the truth.
你在这儿说的话都不能用来控告你
Anything you admit here can't be used against you,
-好好利用这点  -嗯
- so take advantage of that. - Hmm.
你当律师的第一年就像这样吗
Was your first year anything like this?
不像
No.
但我想我的第四年应该就是这样了
But my guess is my fourth year will be.
事情变得越来越诡异
Things are getting weirder.
确实是  不是吗
They are, aren't they?
这就是现实
It's the world.
你应对得很好
You're weathering it well.
谢谢
Thanks.
你们可以进来了
You can go in now.
深呼吸  保持微笑
Breathe and smile.
不是吧
Oh, come on!
我当事人接受的是自愿面谈
I brought my client in for a voluntary interview,
不是小组审讯
not a group interrogation!
那和你们没关系  我们到里面
That's not for you. We're in here.
进来吧  他们不咬人的
Come on, they won't bite.
让她们过来  伙计们
Let 'em through, guys.
抱歉  走廊正在进行粉刷
Sorry, they're painting in the hallway,
来这里只能通过第六度空间
and, uh, the only way in is through the sixth degree room.
对此深表歉意
So, sorry about that.
你好  我是卢卡·奎恩
Hi, I'm Lucca Quinn.
-你好  -这是我当事人  玛娅·林德尔
- Hi. - This is my client, Maia Rindell.
我知道  国安局把你们通讯的邮件发过来了
Hi, yeah, I know, the NSA sent over some of your e-mails.
开个玩笑
That's a joke.
我今天特精神
I'm punchy today.
我是联邦探员马德琳·斯达克
I'm Federal Agent Madeline Starkey.
我们还是坐着聊聊吧
And, uh, why don't we have a seat and chat?
-坐这里  -谢谢
- There you go. - Thank you.
我有点气喘
I'm out of breath.
玛娅  非常感谢你今天能来
So, Maia, thank you so much for coming today.
我们很感激你能协助这次调查
Um, we really appreciate your help with this investigation,
我知道这对你来说不容易
I know this has not been easy on you.
你知道玛娅来这里是受到联邦检察院
you understand Maia is here under the terms of the proffer
提出的供证协议保护吧
from the U.S. Attorney's Office?
当然  这是你们的「一日皇后会谈」  没错
Absolutely, this is your Queen for a Day session, yes.
我当事人说的话都不能用来指控她
Nothing my client says can be used against her.
如果她如实作答
If she answers truthfully,
是这样的  我知道你会这么做的
that is correct and I know you will.
因为向联邦探员说谎可是重罪
Because it's a felony to lie to a, um, federal agent.
「美国法典」第18编第1001条
18 usc 1001.
完全正确
Wow, that's exactly right.
所以  那你清楚如果你说谎的话
So, you understand that the proffer
本供证协议就作废
doesn't immunize you from perjury?
-我知道  -那好
- I do. - Great.
好  那我们开始吧
Good. So, here we are.
天呐
Ooh, my gosh!
你看到刚刚那幕了吗
You see what happened there?
当阳光以某种特定方式
As the light hits the window,
洒向窗户时
you know, in a particular way,
小鸟也会跟着撞上去
the birds fly right into it.
真是悲剧
It's sad, really.
如果律师没有异议
Okay, um, I am going to take some notes,
我得做些笔录
if that's all right with counsel?
没问题
Go for it.
玛娅  我们来谈谈你父母
Maia, let's talk about your parents.
这个庞氏骗局因何而起
How did this Ponzi scheme begin?
玛娅不知道这次庞氏骗局的起因
Uh, Maia doesn't know how this Ponzi scheme began.
对  对  是我的错
Oh, right, right. My apologies.
那我表述范围再大些
Um, let me be a little more discursive.
这样来说吧
Let's look at this as:
和庞氏骗局相关的记忆
Remembrance of Ponzi Schemes Past, huh?
你想起任何关于
And, um, anything that comes into your mind
与你父母或是贾克斯叔叔相关的
about your parents or your Uncle Jackson,
都可以说出来  好吗
you just spill it, okay?
我就坐在这里  把这些记录下来
And I'll just sit here and I'll write it down.
戴安  我需要你
Diane, I need you.
我们接到法院一通电话
We got a call from the courthouse.
又是一桩暴力执法案
Another brutality case.
现在
Now?
猜猜涉案警察是谁
Guess who the cop is?
我猜不到  阿德里安
I'm bad at this, Adrian.
安德鲁·泰鲁
Andrew Theroux.
-你当真吗  -千真万确
- Seriously? - Seriously.
那桩促使我们联盟的案子
The case that brought us together, hmm?
他因过期车标拦下一名摩托车司机
He stops a motorist for expired tags,
踢了他的头
kicks him in the head.
你怎么知道的
How do you know this?
我在县里安插了眼线
I have somebody down at County.
他每向我通报一件暴力执法事件就会拿到300美元
I pay him $300 if he gives me a heads-up on brutality cases.
我们要把这个黑警永远地踢出警局
So we can get this dirty cop off the force once and for all.
-早上好  -早上好
- Good mornin'. - Mornin'.
有什么消息
What do we got?
这是我近期见过的最恶劣事件之一
This is one of the worst I've seen in a while.
有人来看他吗
Anybody else seen him?
家人  律师  有吗
Uh, the family members? Lawyers? Anybody?
没有  泰鲁昨晚才把他弄进来
No. Theroux brought his load in last night.
他归你管
He's all yours.
好
Good.
给我们半个小时
Give us a half-hour with him.
你们是我的律师吗
Are you my lawyers?
但愿如此  您贵姓
We hope to be, Mr...
努特森  托德·努特森
Knutsen. Todd Knutsen.
听我说  不是我干的
Look, I didn't do it.
那警察直接对我的车进行了搜查
The cop just searched my car.
什么时候
When was this?
昨晚  大概午夜时分
Last night, about midnight.
看来他们把你伤口处理得不错
It looks like they, uh, cleaned up your injuries pretty good.
他踢你哪里了
Wh-Where'd he kick you?
我应该说他踢我了吗
Should I say he kicked me?
你是为何被抓进来的  孩子
What are you in for, son?
私藏毒品
Possession.
警卫
Guard!
哪里有抹布
Ugh, where are the Handi Wipes?
我需要普瑞来洗手液
I need my Purell.
简直在虐待我
This is abuse.
天呐
Oh, dear God.
戴安·洛克哈特
Diane Lockhart.
感谢上帝
Ah... Thank God.
艾丽西娅给你打电话了吗
Did Alicia call you?
她说她不能接我的案子
She said she couldn't take my case.
没有  所以你才是暴力执法的受害者
No. So you're the brutality victim?
这是不是糟透了
Isn't it terrible?
我...  看这里
I... Look at this. Hmm? Hmm?
你知道把血渍从埃及棉面料
Do you have any idea how hard it is
清洗掉得有多难
to get blood out of Egyptian cotton?
而且还没有普瑞来
Oh... And now no Purell.
我载着奈芙塔莉
I was driving down 290
凌晨两点驱车行驶在290公路上
around 2:00 in the morning with Naftali.
-她是谁  -一个朋友
- Who's that? - A-A friend.
极具冒险精神  以色列人
Adventurous. Israeli.
她父亲以前是将军
Her father was a general.
千万别和她提「六日战争」
Don't get her started on the Six-Day War.
第三次中东战争  以色列方面称六日战争
她就喜欢看我受苦
She loves seeing me in pain.
你脸上的淤伤
The bruises on your face.
我们怎么知道不是奈芙塔莉弄的
How do we know those aren't from Naftali?
不  奈芙塔莉绝不会对我的脸动手
No. Naftali knows never to hit me in the face,
只有背部和大腿
only the back and the thighs.
所以你背部和大腿都有淤伤吗
So you have bruises on your back and your thighs?
很轻的淤伤
Mmm, slight bruises.
大部分是些抓痕
Mostly scratches.
那女人单凭一根回形针就能让人欲仙欲死
What that woman can do with the end of a paper clip...
我知道  我不是一名好的目击者
I know. I'm not a good witness.
和她谈谈...  奈芙塔莉·阿马多
Talk to her... Naftali Amado.
-她和我的口径肯定一致  -好
- She'll say exactly what I said. - Okay.
他们逮捕我的方式
They're out to get me.
和对待罗德尼·金是如出一辙
The same way they did with Rodney King.
罗德尼·金：警方暴力执法的受害者  法院判决四名白人警察无罪
从而引发1992年洛杉矶暴动
我们有很多的共同点  他和我
We've got a lot in common, he and I.
我们怎么就不能和平相处呢
Can't we all just get along?
你怎么看
What do you think?
他就是个恶魔
Oh, he's the devil.
不幸的是  这个恶魔是我们将泰鲁
And unfortunately, the devil is our best chance
踢出警局的最好机会
to get Theroux kicked off the force.
我不知道从哪儿说起
I'm not sure how to start.
那不然这样吧
Well, here, let-let's try this.
根据法务会计的报告
From our forensic accounting,
首次出现犯罪行为
the first criminal act...
也即第一次使用新入资金来偿还原先债务
the first one where new funds were used to pay off old debts...
时间是2008年9月15日
was September 15, 2008.
想起什么了吗
Any thoughts?
这过去太久了
That was a long time ago.
2008年吗
Um, 2008?
我那时17岁
I would have been 17.
你记得那天你在做什么吗
And do you remember what you were doing that day?
我大概在学校
I was probably in school.
好吧  那天雷曼兄弟破产了
Okay. Well, it was the day Lehman Brothers went bankrupt.
这能帮你回忆起什么吗
Does that help?
突发新闻  全球股票进入暴跌状态
Breaking news. Stocks all around the globe are in a freefall at this point,
-危机产生于...  -我的天呐
- because of the crisis of... - Holy God.
道琼斯工业指数预计会下降300点
The Dow expected to open down over 300 points,
-恐慌的产生... -天呐  什么
- as fears of... - Uh, God... What?
不管能想起什么都行
Anything you remember could help.
如果你记不清  直说记不清就好
If you're not sure of a memory, just say you're not sure.
突发新闻  雷曼兄弟已穷途末路
天呐  我们要怎么解释啊
Oh, God. What...uh, uh, what are we gonna say?
-我要怎么办啊  -别慌  别这样
- What am I gonna do? - Stop. Stop it!
我们得联系贾克斯
We just have to get Jax.
我一整天都在打电话
I-I've been all day making calls...
玛娅  你记得这个名字吗
Maia, do you recognize this name?
迈克尔·汉尼根
Michael Hannigan.
他是你父母基金的一位投资人
He was an investor in your parent's fund.
-记得  -他9月15日那天在你家吗
- Yes. - And he was at your house on September 15?
-没错  -好的
- Yes. - Okay.
你父母和他说话了吗
And your parents spoke with him?
是的
Yes.
贾克斯也在
Jax was there, too.
我叔叔贾克斯也在  他们聊了会儿
Um, my Uncle Jax, he was there and-and spoke to him.
是和汉尼根吗  你确定吗
To Hannigan? You're sure?
这只是暂时的  迈克尔
This is temporary, Mike.
你现在撤回投资  就损失了八百万...
You pull your money out now, you're out eight mil...
我确定
Yes.
我妈妈  她给贾克斯打了电话
My mom, she, uh, uh, she called Jax
他过来告诉迈克尔·汉尼根
and he came over to tell Mike Hannigan that
如果他现在从基金里撤回投资
if he pulled his money from the Fund,
他就可能会损失八百万
then he would be out something like $8 million.
最好别把钱提出来
And the best course was to keep his money in.
贾克斯是什么时候过来的
And what time did Jax come by?
我那时还在做作业
I was still doing my homework.
所以...
Uh, so...
大约是下午四点左右
probably about 4:00 in the afternoon.
好的  他呆了多久
Okay. And how long was he there?
我想大概是两小时
I think two hours.
因为他  他晚饭前就走了
Because he was... he was gone before dinner.
你和你父母一起吃的晚饭吗
And you had dinner with your parents?
你不能永远保证说有12%的收益
You can't always be promising 12%.
这和我们保证多少没关系
Well, it's not about what we prom...
是的
Yes.
好的  现在问题是这样的  玛娅
Good. Now, here's the problem, Maia.
我有你母亲的电子日历  然后
I have your mother's computer calendar, and, uh...
抱歉  我还是有些卢德主义
If you'll pardon me, I'm still a bit of a Luddite.
卢德主义  指对新技术和新事物的一种盲目冲动反抗
我得把它们打印出来
I need it printed out, and, uh...
"卢德"  我真讨厌这个词  你呢
"Luddite," God, I hate that word, don't you?
我对此没什么看法
I don't think I have an opinion.
就像"模因"一样  就是这些词
It's like "Meme." It's one of those words
通过模仿传递行为或思想
让英语显得这么丑陋
that makes the English language so ugly.
-说日历  -好的  你母亲在这天
- The calendar. - Yes. So on this day, your mother
记录说你在下午三点约了妇科医生
says you had a gynecologist appointment at 3:00 p.m.,
和一个叫雷吉娜医生
uh, with a Dr. Regina.
那么问题来了
So here's the problem,
我不知道你是怎么看到
I'm not sure how you could have seen
你叔叔贾克斯在下午四点到你家的
your Uncle Jax at your house at 4:00 p.m.
因为你在下午三点约了医生
when you were at a doctor's appointment at 3:00 p.m.
容我打断一下  你问的可是九年前的事
Excuse me, you're asking about something that happened nine years ago.
我知道  听着  我是站在你这边的
Oh, I know. Look, I'm on your side in this.
我知道记忆可能会有偏差
I know that memory can be faulty.
我只是试图找到真相而已
I'm just trying to get to the truth.
玛娅
Maia.
你有去医生那儿吗
Were you there at the doctor's appointment?
去了
I was.
可能我是后来才看到贾克斯和汉尼根先生的
Uh, maybe I-I saw Jax and Mr. Hannigan later.
或许是另一天的事
Or another day, maybe?
不  我不这么认为
No. No, I don't think so.
-就在那天  -那问题来了
- It... it was on that day. - Well, here's the problem.
雷吉娜医生的办公室
The distance between Dr. Regina's office
和你家的距离是12.4英里
and your house is 12.4 miles,
那天路上还特别的堵
and it was very, very heavy traffic that day.
你是怎么知道的
How do we know that?
我联调局的属下们  他们无所不知
My minions, my FBI minions. They know everything.
还给了我打印稿
And they give me hard copies.
那么你和你母亲回家的时候
So by the time you would get home with your mother
就已经五点半了
it would have been 5:30.
你管家也说她是五点半给你端上的晚餐
And your housekeeper said she served you dinner right at 5:30.
贾克斯怎么说的
What did Jax say?
贾克斯说他那天从没去过你家
Jax... says he was never at your house at all.
他在说谎  他去了
That is not true. He was there.
但你记不清时间
But you can't remember when.
是的  但我...
No. No, but I...
我记得他在那儿
I remember that he was there.
大概在我八岁的时候
You know, when I was, uh, about eight,
我去看了「波索马戏团」
I was on Bozo's Circus.
儿童节目
你那时还没到记事的年纪
And, uh... you're too young to remember this...
但那时可是很出名的节目
but it was a really big deal.
我和妈妈坐在观众席里
I was sitting in the audience with my mom,
我被抽中玩特等奖游戏
and I was chosen for the grand prize game,
这更是大事件了
which is another very big deal.
我记得我把球投中了六号框
And I remember as I got that ball into bucket number six,
到处都是彩屑
and the confetti was all over the place,
观众在欢呼
the crowd was roaring.
而到去年
And last year
我妈妈给我看了那天的照片
my mother showed me some pictures from that day.
我没去看「波索马戏团」
I wasn't on the Bozo show.
是我姐姐去了
My older sister was.
你看  人的思维很奇异
See, the mind has an odd way of turning
能把美好想象变成真实记忆
wishful thinking into actual memories.
好吧
Okay...
我觉得我们得暂停一会儿
I think we should take a pause there.
我得和我的当事人商量下
I want to confer with my client.
没问题  请便  请记住
Oh, absolutely. Please. And remember,
这是一日皇后会谈
this is Queen for a Day,
问的问题都没有任何陷阱
so no gotcha questions here.
走那边  走那边
Go around, go around!
油漆工在忙  抱歉
Painters. Sorry.
从那扇门出去
Uh, just go out that door.
你们来的那扇门
Door you came.
抱歉  我们只是...
Uh, sorry. We're just, uh...
那边油漆工不让过  所以...
There's just painters, so...
好了  我的建议是
Okay, here's my advice.
她不是你朋友  她想揪到你的谎言
She is not your friend. She's trying to catch you in lies.
-我没撒谎  -我明白的
- I'm not lying. - I understand.
我知道你想保护你父母
I know you're trying to protect your parents,
但她知道你在试图这样做
but she can see you're doing that.
所以别说贾克斯和汉尼根碰面的事
So don't talk about Jax being with Hannigan
除非你清楚记得是那样
unless you have a specific memory.
我不想害我爸爸
I don't want to hurt my dad.
我明白
I know.
但供证协议的前提是你会说实话
But your proffer only covers you if you don't lie.
如果你为了保护父亲撒谎  他可能会脱罪
If you lie to protect your dad, you might get him off,
但你会进监狱
but you'll end up in jail.
全体起立
All rise.
有请尊敬的法官唐·林登
The Honorable Don Linden presiding.
不  史蒂夫  我能自己来
Uh, n-uh, no, Steve, I have it.
不用
No.
好吧
Okay.
我想这次我赌赢了
Well, I guess I won that bet.
斯威尼先生又来了  这真是太好了
Mr. Sweeney, how nice of you to join us again.
我是无辜的  法官阁下
I am innocent man, Your Honor.
法官阁下
Your Honor,
我们的当事人和这个社区有着很深的渊源
our client has very deep roots in his community...
在奥黑尔机场还有私人飞机
And a private jet on standby at O'Hare.
什么指控
Okay, what is the charge?
唐·林登法官
-拒捕  -严重伤害
- Resisting arrest. - Aggravated battery.
不  严重伤害
No. Aggravated battery.
等等  什么
Wait, what?
法官阁下  这是轻罪
Your Honor, this is a misdemeanor.
不  重罪
No, a felony.
斯威尼先生殴打警官
Now, Mr. Sweeney struck out at the officer,
重击其头部和面部
striking him in the head and face.
这简直是令人作呕的过度指控
This is gross overcharging.
-众生平等  -别卖乖  先生
- All lives matter. - Don't get cute, sir.
闭嘴  科林  我好不容易站在你这边的
Shut up, Colin. I'm finally on your side.
法官阁下  我们请求
Your Honor, we ask that
在斯威尼先生本人担保下将其释放
Mr. Sweeney be released on his own recognizance.
他是过分控告的受害者
He's a victim of overzealous prosecution.
他被人当成靶子了  法官阁下
He all but has a target on his back, Your Honor.
是吗  我想知道为什么
Oh, gee, I wonder why.
保释金定为三百万美元
Bail is set at three million dollars.
下一个
Next.
-阿提卡  阿提卡  -嘘
- Attica. Attica. - Shh.
美国纽约监狱
1971年9月9日至13日阿提卡监狱曾发生犯人暴动  死43人
你在笑  为什么
You're smiling. Why?
对警官严重伤害的重罪
Felony aggravated battery against a police officer.
我们可以让泰鲁上证人席吗
We can put Theroux on the stand?
当然
Yup.
如果他们指控轻罪的话  我们就不能
If they kept it a misdemeanor, we couldn't.
科林·斯威尼终于要做件好事了
So Colin Sweeney is gonna do his one good deed:
把坏条子从警察队伍中踢出去
get a dirty cop kicked off the force.
是的  你们错过了一整个鸟群
Yup, you missed an entire flock.
你们两个把要解决的事情都解决好了吗
Did you two get everything settled?
没什么要解决的
There was nothing to settle.
但是我们谈了谈  然后我们回来了
But we talked. And we're back.
好  很好  很好
Good. Good, good, good.
玛娅  我想让你看看你母亲的行程表
So, Maia, I want you to take a look at your mother's calendar, okay?
你会看到
I think you'll see that
列出了过去的几年里你们两人的会面
you two have a few appointments listed over the years,
而且不止是妇科检查  看到了吗
and not just the gyno. See?
比如  10月3日那天你有另一个约会
For example, on October 3 you had another appointment
跟雷吉娜医生  还有
with Dr. Regina. And, uh,
2008年10月
然后  10月23日
then, on October 23
你陪你母亲一起去检查了牙齿
you went with your mother to her dental checkup.
23日
玛娅牙科检查
上午十点
然后11月4日  你俩去看了电影
And then on November 4, the two of you went to see a movie.
你还记得看的是什么吗
Do you remember what you saw?
-不记得  -你好好看一下
- No. - Yeah, well, why don't you take a good look at that and,
在你记得的那些旁边打个勾
put a check mark next to the ones that you remember.
我担心的不是性病
Well, the worry is not STD...
2008年10月
3日 玛娅的妇科检查  下午三点
雷吉娜医生
玛娅有个男朋友
Maia has a boyfr...
19日
玛娅的妇科检查
下午三点半
瑞吉娜医生
医生  我能做些什么呢
What can I do to help, doct...
17日
玛娅妇科检查
下午三点半
雷吉娜医生
谢谢
Thank you.
所以这几次你都跟你妈在一起
So you and your mom were together at these times?
是的
Yes.
我记得是这样的
As far as I remember, yes.
好的
Okay.
有个问题
Well, here's the problem...
如果有问题的时候
It would be easier if you would just
你提前告诉我们会好一些
tell us a problem before there is a problem.
你母亲这几次并没有跟你在一起
Your mother wasn't with you at these appointments.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
那是她开溜跟你叔叔贾克斯滚床单的日子
That's when she was off sleeping with your Uncle Jax.
她在行程表上把这些预约当做借口
She used as an excuse these appointments in her calendar
这样她就能跟你叔叔贾克斯在他家约会了
so she could meet with your Uncle Jax at his home.
玛娅根本没有可能知道的
Maia had no way to know that.
是的  就是因为她母亲写进行程表里的
Yes, but just because her mother has it in her calendar
并不一定就是真的
doesn't mean it's true.
如果不是事实的话
And Maia shouldn't confirm it
玛娅就不应该确认
if it's not true.
其中的一些日期是真的
Some of those dates are true.
没有一个是真的  玛娅
None of these dates are true, Maia.
每两周
Every two weeks,
你母亲都会和你叔叔贾克斯在他家约会
your mother met with your Uncle Jax at his home.
从2008年开始
Since 2008.
有没有可能你母亲跟你叔叔联手
Is it possible that your mother is working
陷害你的父亲呢
with your Uncle Jax to set up your Dad?
我的当事人无法回答
My client cannot answer that.
这就是问题  玛娅
'Cause here's the problem, Maia.
这几年来
You were used as a cover
你都被你母亲当做跟你叔叔鬼混的借口
so your mother could sleep with your uncle for several years.
而你从未起过任何疑心
And you didn't suspect anything?
-没有  -好的
- No. - Okay.
与此同时
And in that same time frame,
你怀疑过你父母的庞氏骗局吗
did you ever suspect your parents of their Ponzi scheme?
我觉得我们这会儿应该午休一下
I think we should take a break for lunch at this point.
-我想继续问几个小时  -不行
- I'd like to go for a few more hours. - No.
我们休息一下
Let's take a break.
好吧  如果你们执意如此
Sure. If you insist.
上午11点16分
纳特  你应该去补补觉
Nat, you need to get some sleep.
是啊  你以为我在干什么
Yeah, what do you think I'm doing?
我们又有一个被警察暴力执法的当事人了
We have another client who was brutalized by a cop.
你们知道我是给平民警察问责办公室工作的
You do know I work for COPA,
-而不是给你们卖命的  -平民警察问责办公室
- not for you? - Civilian Office of Police Accountability.
就怕你没意识到  我们就是平民
Just in case you haven't noticed, we are civilians.
你们不是平民  你们是寄生虫
You're not civilians, you're parasites.
纳特  当时在例行交通管制期间
It was during a routine traffic stop, Nat.
你最好还是拿笔记下来
You'll want to write this down.
你猜警察是谁
Guess who the cop is?
安德鲁·泰鲁
Andrew Theroux.
什么时候的事
And when-when was this?
昨晚
Last night.
-你们要起诉吗  -是的
- You're bringing a suit? - Yup.
-再告六百万  -受害者是谁
- Another six million. - Who's the victim?
每个市民都享有同等的受法律保护的权利吧
All right, every citizen deserves equal protection under the law.
-受害者是谁  -给他个机会
- Who's the victim? - Give him a chance.
-他并没做错什么  -阿德里安
- He hasn't done anything wrong. - Adrian.
科林·斯威尼
Colin Sweeney.
好吧  好吧
All right. Okay, okay.
这些警察一直跟着人家屁股后面
The cops have been following this guy around,
想找借口报复
looking for some kind of payback.
他把他拽出车外
He dragged him out of the car
踢了他的头
and kicked him in the head.
平民警察问责办公室得调查
COPA has to investigate.
在这事上科林·斯威尼不是重点
Now, you know it's not about Sweeney,
关键是要把这混蛋踢出去警队  来吧
it's about getting this piece of shit off the force. Come on.
来上庭  我们让泰鲁上证人席
Come to court. We're gonna put Theroux on the stand. -
我就是不想要有成见
All I want is an open mind.
来吧
Come on.
是内务部吗  是平民警察问责办公室
That was Internal Affairs? That was COPA.
而且他们不会调查的
And they're not gonna investigate.
在证人席上把泰鲁问垮
Destroy Theroux on the stand.
他会回来的
He'll be back.
一开始他情绪激动  后来他就开始动手了
At first he was agitated, then he got belligerent.
在我看来他像是嗑药了
It seemed to me that he was on drugs.
我都二十年没嗑过药了
I haven't used drugs in 20 years.
小点声嘀咕  斯威尼先生
Whisper quieter, Mr. Sweeney.
-我在这都能听见  -对不起法官阁下
- I can hear you up here. - Sorry, Your Honor.
我估计昨晚警官打我的时候
I think my eardrum is damaged
我的耳膜可能受损了
from when the officer hit me last night.
反对  法官阁下
Objection, Your Honor.
反对有效  闭嘴  斯威尼先生
Sustained. Shut up, Mr. Sweeney.
对于他的反抗  你是如何反应的呢  警官
And how did you react to his struggle, officer?
我尽量只用必要的力量
I tried to use only as much force as was necessary
使他屈服
to gain his compliance.
不幸的是  他攻击我
Unfortunately, he chose to attack me,
很遗憾地说
and, I'm sorry to say,
-造成了一些损伤  -这里和这里的瘀伤吗
- did some damage. - These bruises here and here?
-是的  先生  -如果是我干的
- Yes, sir. - If I did that, don't you think
你不觉得我手上应该有痕迹吗
I'd have some marks on my hands?
还有我嘴里的伤口
Also cuts inside my mouth
我的医生认为我需要进行一些矫正手术
My doctor believes I'll need to have some corrective surgery
来重新排齐我的牙齿
in order to reset my teeth.
杰  是我  黛安
Jay. It's Diane.
我刚给你转了一张泰鲁伤口的照片
I just forwarded you a picture of Theroux's injuries.
我都没想到过要说这个  但是我认为
I never thought I'd say this, but I think there's a chance
科林·斯威尼有可能说的是实话
Colin Sweeney is telling the truth.
常用联系人
艾米
艾米办公室
爸爸
妈妈
玛娅  我们该进去了
Maia. We're back in.
希望你们都享用了美妙的午餐
Well, I hope you both had a nice lunch.
我希望这次调查能控制在三个小时之内
I'd like to keep this under three hours. -
没问题  吃吗
Certainly. See's?
不用了  谢谢
No, thank you.
-吃吗  -不了
- See's? - No.
我老公把好吃的都捡了出来
My husband picked out all the good stuff
就给我留了点椰子味的带来上班吃
and sent me to work with the coconuts.
你老公叫什么名字
What's your husband's name?
迈克尔  森  怎么了
Michael... son. Why?
你们结婚多久了
How long have you two been married?
我吃午饭时用谷歌搜了你
I googled you over lunch.
你没有结婚
You're not married.
被你发现了
You got me.
你还协助定了
You were also instrumental in the convictions
布拉戈耶维奇和乔治·赖安的罪
of Blagojevich and George Ryan.
伊利诺伊州的两任州长  被定贪污罪入狱
这样示好对他们也起作用了吗
Did the folksy thing work on them, too?
以前有一位律师  我负责案子的律师...
Well, there was one lawyer, uh, in one of the cases...
我不会指名道姓
and I'm not gonna say who...
我们对他的客户没有兴趣
we weren't interested in his client.
我们只要求他前来做一次惯例询问
We only asked him to come in for a how-do-you-do meeting.
但这位律师非常咄咄逼人
but this lawyer was so aggressive
疑心很重  于是我们就决定
and so suspicious that we decided
进一步调查他的客户
to probe further into his client.
而现在他的客户进了监狱
And that client is now in prison.
-很好的故事  -真人真事
- Sweet story. - Well, it's a true one.
你是在建议我  不要代表我的客户吗
Are you advising me - not to represent my client?
我完全没有这个意思
Oh, far from it.
我觉得如果玛娅能说出她知道的所有事情
I think it would benefit both of us
对我们都有利
if Maia were to offer all she knows.
毫无保留
Undiluted.
你想知道什么  斯达克女士
What do you need, Ms. Starkey?
我想谈谈这个基金
Well, I'd like to turn to the foundation.
林德尔基金
The... the Rindell Foundation.
你是三个董事会成员之一吗
You're one of three board members?
是的
Uh, yes.
你...
And you...
上一次董事会是什么时候
When was the last time the board met?
我不知道
I don't know.
几年前吧
a few years ago?
如果你已经知道了请直接告诉她
If you have the answer you can just tell her.
我觉得最后一次董事会
I think the last board meeting
也是仅有的一次董事会
and only board meeting
是在2011年6月18日
was June 18, 2011.
据你所知在其它时间还开过董事会吗
Do you know of any other dates? Any more meetings?
-没有了  -好吧  你不觉得奇怪吗
- No. - Okay. That doesn't bother you?
-请告诉我你是什么意思  -这个基金
- Tell me what you mean. - Well, it's a foundation
资产达到了6500万美元...
with $65 million in assets...
而你们只开过一次会
and you only met once?
建立这个基金并不是我的意思
Well, the foundation wasn't my idea.
-是...  -是你父母的主意  是的
- It was... It was your parents, yeah.
是的  而且是做善事的
Yes, but it was for a good cause.
为了非洲的疟疾预防
For malaria prevention in Africa.
那你们在预防疟疾上投入了多少资金
Oh, and how much did you spend on prevention?
是的  但是...
Yeah, but...
我就是想知道我们给他们送了多少钱
I just want to know how much we're sending.
亲爱的  你知道  挺多钱的  亲爱的
Honey. You know, it's a lot, uh, honey.
我们不会克扣的
I mean, we're not skimping.
-我不知道  -没关系  玛娅
- I don't know. - Oh, well, that's okay, Maia.
你只是有名无实  这不是件坏事
You were a figurehead. That's not a bad thing.
你不会有麻烦的
You're not in trouble.
但是爸  基金有我的名字
Yeah, but Dad, I mean, it's got my name on it.
我有权知道
I have to know.
好吧  我让贾克斯把账目给你看
Okay, I'll-I'll have Jax open the books to you.
给我们几个星期时间
Just give us a few weeks.
-好吧  -好吧
- Okay. - Okay.
你需要休息一会儿吗
Do you need a moment?
不用了
No.
那我们就来谈谈基金成立的日期吧
So let's talk about the day the foundation was formed.
-搞到了吗  -就是这个
- Did you get it? - Right here.
-书面陈述呢  -在这里
- Affidavits? - Here.
你刚救了他一命  很感谢  杰
You just saved his ass. Thank you, Jay.
很好
Good to know.
你好  泰鲁警官
Hello, Officer Theroux.
你好
Hello.
你之前也在这里
This is a familiar spot for you...
接受了关于警察施暴案的询问
being questioned about police brutality.
反对  诱导性问题  非常无理
Objection. Argumentative. And rude.
第一项反对有效
Sustained to the first.
第二项反对无效
Overruled to the second.
警官  你是在萨沃伊健身馆锻炼吗
Officer, do you work out at Savoy's Gym?
是的  怎么了
Yes, why?
你记得昨天下午曾与一位名叫
Do you recall yesterday afternoon sparring
赫克托·佩拉萨的19岁的
with a 19-year-old welterweight
次中量级拳击手过招吗
named Hector Peraza
根据一位目击证人的证词
who, according to eyewitnesses,
-他曾打败过你  -胡说八道...
- knocked you out? - That's bullshit...
他没打败我
he didn't knock me out.
抱歉  但你与他打过拳击吗
My apologies. But you sparred with him?
是的  我坚持到了最后
Yeah, I held my own.
这是在你值班之前的事吗
And this was before - you went on duty?
是的  怎么了
Yes. Why?
那有没有可能  你脸上的淤青
Well, isn't it possible that these bruises here are the result
是由赫克托·佩拉萨造成的
of punches thrown by Hector Peraza?
-不是  -好吧  这些的你嘴巴内部的
- No. - Well, these are photos
切割和撕裂伤口的照片
of cuts and lacerations inside your mouth,
-泰鲁警官  -反对  不在证据列表中
- Officer Theroux. - Objection. Not in evidence.
这些是警方的照片  法官阁下
These are police photos, Your Honor.
不是我们拍的
We didn't take them.
除非你想把你们所有的照片都剔除出去
Unless you want to throw out all your photos,
助理检察官先生  反对无效
Mr. ASA, overruled.
你看见这些伤口了吗  泰鲁警官
Do you see these lacerations, Officer Theroux?
这些撕裂伤和这东西的形状相符
Those lacerations are in the same shape as this.
萨沃伊健身馆的护口器
The mouth guard at Savoy's Gym.
你们太厉害了
You guys are good.
*祝你生日快乐*
*Happy birthday to you*
*祝你生日快乐...*
*Happy birthday to you...*
是你18岁的生日吗
So this was your 18th birthday?
是的
Yes.
你父母就是在那个时候将林德尔基金送给你的
And that's when your parents gifted you the Rindell Foundation?
是的
Yes.
林德尔基金
我爸妈  他们知道我对非洲很感兴趣
My parents, they-they knew I was interested in Africa.
我听说疟疾一年能夺去一百万个孩子的生命
I had read that malaria kills one million kids a year
而蚊帐就能阻止这种疾病蔓延
and that it could be prevented with mosquito netting.
所以他们想我为资助非洲百分之六十的孩子
So they wanted me to run an effort to pay for the netting
买蚊帐出一份力
for 60% of African children.
确实目的很崇高
Well, that is a good cause,
非常感谢你的善举
and thank you so much for doing that.
我能问一下还有谁参加了那场聚会吗
Can I ask you who else was at your party?
很多人
A lot of people.
你的女朋友呢  艾米·布雷斯林
How 'bout your girlfriend, uh, Amy Breslin?
是的  她也在
Yes, she was there.
但她当时不是我的女朋友
But she wasn't my girlfriend at the time.
是贾克斯叔叔介绍我们认识的
Uncle Jax introduced us.
她当时刚进法学院
She was just entering law school.
你男朋友也在吗
And your boyfriend was there, too?
我得回去了
I have to get back.
玛娅  他在场吗
Maia, was he there?
-是的  -好的
- Yes. - Okay.
并没有很复杂
Well, that's not complicated.
好吧
Okay.
还有戴安·洛哈特  她在吗
And Diane Lockhart, was she there?
是的  她也在
Yes, she was there, too.
你确定不想来一块吗  很好吃的
You sure you don't want one? They're delicious.
你老公送的吗
From your husband?
好吧
Okay.
现在你听见过洛哈特女士有给你的父母
Now, did you hear Ms. Lockhart offer any legal advice
任何法律建议吗
to your parents?
好了  我要你就此打住
Okay, I'm gonna stop you right there.
这些内容不在供证协议的范围中
This is not material covered by the proffer.
所有与庞氏骗局有关的事情
Well, anything that has to do with the Ponzi scheme
都涵盖在了这份供证协议中
is covered by the proffer.
受到律师与当事人的保密特权保护的
Hearsay conversations which, in fact,
传闻证据对话内容  不能...
may be subject to attorney-client privilege are not...
我现在手头的案子是个谋杀案
Actually, my current case is a homicide.
我的客户被指控杀死了一位
My client is accused of killing a mutual fund manager
与伯尼·麦道夫共事的互惠基金经理
who worked with Bernie Madoff.
真的假的
Really?
你认识他吗
Do you know him?
伯尼  不认识
Bernie? No.
我们认识他吗  丽诺
Do we, Lenore?
也许贾克斯认识吧  我不知道
Maybe Jax... I don't know.
我想问的只是她有没有印象  如果她没有
All I'm asking is if she has a memory. If she doesn't,
-我们可以继续  -我想说的不是这个
- we can move on... - That's not what I'm saying...
我得回去了
I have to get back.
-打电话给我  -等等
- Call me. - Wait, wait, wait.
我想说的只是如果她有印象
All I'm saying is if she has a memory,
你这是在进行钓鱼式盘问
This is a fishing expedition on your part.
-我会听的  不然我们  -你在刨根问底
- I will hear it, or we'll... - You are digging.
-不不不  -丽诺  你觉得露丝·麦道夫
- No, no, no, no... - Lenore, do you think that Ruth Madoff knew
知道她丈夫在做什么吗
what her husband was doing?
我觉得不知道  为什么这么问
No. Why?
是这样的  我觉得她不知道是因为她不想知道
See, I think she didn't know because she didn't want to know.
是啊
Yeah.
她怎么会不知道呢
How could she not know?
-我会听的  不然我们  -你在刨根问底
- ...I will hear it, or we'll... - You are digging.
不不不不  打住  等一下
No, no, no, no, no. Hold on. Just a sec.
问题是这样的  奎因女士
Here's the problem, Ms. Quinn...
我们手上有一大堆问题不是吗
We have a lot of problems here, don't we?
这些基金会的文件是玛娅签署的
...these foundation documents were signed by Maia.
林德尔基金会
她不仅签了字  而且如她刚刚所承认的
And she signed them, she just admitted,
她是在她18岁生日当晚签的字
on the night of her birthday party, her 18th birthday.
所以她对这个基金会
So she is responsible
产生的所有违法行为负有法律责任
for any crimes committed by this foundation.
我们的供证协议是基于玛娅和基金会的关联
Our proffer is about Maia's involvement with this fund,
而不是戴安·洛哈特的建议
not Diane Lockhart's advice...
我不想做坏人
I hate to be the bad guy here,
但是数百万美元的资金驻留在那个基金会中
but millions of dollars were being parked into that foundation
以躲避证监会的审计
to hide them from an SEC audit.
这可是重罪
That is a felony crime.
那么现在  除非玛娅告诉我们戴安·洛哈特
Now, unless Maia tells us about Diane Lockhart's advice
林德尔基金会
给了她父母什么建议  不然我们现在就停止盘问
to her parents, we will stop this questioning now
并对她提起指控
and prosecute.
我需要年满18岁才能让那些文件生效对吗
I need to be 18 for those documents to be official?
是的  而你当时年满18了
Yes. And you were.
你在18岁生日当天签的这些协议
You signed them on your 18th birthday.
我的18岁生日派对是周六举行的
We had my birthday party on a Saturday,
直到下个周二我才年满18岁
and I didn't turn 18 until the following Tuesday.
不是吧
Come on.
你知道吗
You know,
也许我是该尝一颗糖
maybe I will have one of those candies.
手段不错  探员
Nice try, Agent.
你当时对付布拉戈耶维奇也是用的这个手段吗
Is this the kind of finesse you used on Blagojevich?
干得漂亮  玛娅
Nice, Maia.
只是运气好
Lucky.
不  我见过什么叫走好运
No, I've seen lucky.
刚刚那叫聪明
That was smart.
下午1点27分
我方还要传唤一位证人  法官阁下
I have another witness, Your Honor.
奈芙塔莉·阿马多
Naftali Amado.
我以为你说她是站在你们这边的
I thought you said she was on your side.
她是站在我们这边
She is.
她曾站在我们这边
She was.
奈芙塔莉
Naftali.
你好  阿马多女士
Hello, Ms. Amado.
你好  汉子
Hello, man.
斯威尼先生被叫住靠边停车的时候你在他车上
You were with Mr. Sweeney when his car was pulled over,
-对吗  -是的
- isn't that correct? - Ken.
我们在法庭上说英语
We speak English here.
-是的  -希伯来语太让我兴奋了
- Yes. - Hebrew makes me so hot.
你们被叫住靠边停车后发生了什么
And what happened after you were pulled over?
那位警官  他走向我们
The policeman, he comes over to us.
他说  我们需要出示
He says, uh, we need to show the...
那个什么
the, um,
-驾  -驾照
- uh, lice? - License?
对  但是斯威尼先生
Yes. But, uh, Mr. Sweeney
当时脾气非常火爆[性感]
is very, very hot.
他下车
He gets out of the car,
打了那位警官
punches the policeman.
真是岂有此理
That is outrageous.
你才是岂有此理
You are outrageous.
-你  -你给我坐下
- You... - You sit back down.
抱歉  女士  我来说就好
Excuse me, ma'am. That is my job.
请保持克制  斯威尼先生
Please, Mr. Sweeney.
还有别的问题吗  律师
Any more questions, Counselor?
没有了
Nothing further.
粉刷完成了  你们可以从这边进来了
Painting's done. You can come in this way now.
这边请
Here you go.
请坐
Have a seat.
我想先为之前的
I'd like to apologize for the uncomfortable mess...
不愉快道歉
...earlier this afternoon.
都怪我  我的错  抱歉
It was all on me. My bad. I'm sorry.
我不想让我们之间剑拔弩张
I don't want things to be tense between us.
-我们也不想  -很好
- We don't either. - Good.
那么我们重归于好了吗
So we're friends again?
-当然  -好的  很好
- Sure. - Okay. Good.
玛娅  我们来聊聊你是什么时候得知
Maia, um, let's talk about when you did become aware
这场庞氏骗局的
of the Ponzi scheme.
你说是媒体报道时你才得知的
You said it was when the press reported on it.
是的
Yes.
而不是在此之前
And not before?
完全正确
That is correct.
你是2016年从法学院毕业的  对吗
You graduated from law school in 2016, right?
是的
Yes.
那天是不是个大日子
Was it a big day?
我不太明白你的意思
I don't understand.
当天在你父母家有个庆祝会
Well, there was a celebration at your parents' house.
敬美妙的一年
To a fantastic year.
是的  确实有
Yes, there was.
你父母在场吗
Your parents were there?
艾米的父母当时在场吗
Amy's parents were there?
谢谢你们能来  玛娅
Thank you for being here. Oh, Maia...
是的  山姆和康妮
Yes, Sam and Connie.
好的  山姆和康妮
Okay. Sam and Connie.
你当时从法学院
Now, were you living with Amy, uh,
毕业之时和艾米在同居吗
at the time when you graduated from law school?
-是的  -艾米有没有问起过让她父母
- I was. - Did Amy ever ask you about the possibility
投资你父母管理的基金的可行性
of her parents investing in your parents' fund?
她问过
She asked about it.
我告诉她要开设投资账户
And I told her that to start an account,
最低投资金额是20万美元
it-it was a minimum of $200,000.
她的父母拿不出那么多钱
Her parents didn't have that kind of money.
据我了解到的信息  可能不一定对
According to my information... and I could be wrong...
你父母对那个最低投资金额破过例
your parents did make exceptions to that requirement.
那是个问题吗
Is that a question?
不是
No.
这个才是
This is one.
你有没有请求过你父母能不能
Did you ever ask if an exception could be made
为艾米的父母破个例
in the case of Amy's parents?
抱歉
Sorry.
她为什么要撒谎
Why would she lie?
我不知道  她是个调皮的小骚货
I don't know. She's such a naughty minx.
可能她觉得是在开玩笑
It could be her idea of a joke.
斯威尼先生  请认真点
Mr. Sweeney, please take this seriously.
我猜因非法持有毒品
I imagine a felony arrest
导致的被捕会让她被驱逐出境
for drug possession could get her deported.
什么
I'm sorry?
你又是哪位呀
Who are you again?
这间律师的一位合伙人
A partner here.
持有毒品这一说从何而来
Where does the drug possession come in?
犯罪报告里只字未提
There was nothing in the crime report.
那么  合伙人女士
Well, partner,
我就是假设一下
I'm just theorizing here,
但我们当时是在去阿灵顿山庄参加一个
but we were on our way to a chemsex party
-药爱派对的路上  -等等
- in Arlington Heights. - Wait, wait.
我们先打住
We need to stop right there.
你得用假设的语气来说
You need to speak in hypotheticals,
-斯威尼先生  -但是  为什么呢
- Mr. Sweeney. - But... why?
我们不能在明知你会作伪证的情况下让你出庭
We can't put you on the stand knowing you will perjure yourself.
你只能表述真实
You can only relate something that is true
或者潜在真实的事实
or potentially true.
天啊  我爱死法律了
God, I love the law.
每个人都这么认真
And everybody takes it so seriously.
-是你办的派对吗  -没错
- Your party? - Yes.
药爱派对
Chemsex.
药爱  不知道吗
Chemse... No?
兴奋剂鸡尾酒  然后做爱
Drug cocktails, then sex.
极具启发效果
Most enlightening.
-假设来说  -是的
- Hypothetically. - Yes.
假设来说  奈芙塔莉和我
Naftali and I were hypothetically
当时正在去这个派对的途中
on our way to this party, where we were...
而且假设  我们准备吃合成性卡西酮类药物
hypothetically going to supply the synthetic cathinone.
那为什么在警方的报告中
And why was there no mention
没有提到有关毒品的事
of drugs in the police report?
我们停下来的时候
Naftali threw them out the window
奈芙塔莉把药扔出车窗外了
when we were stopped. Uh...
假设来说
Hypothetically.
阿德里安
Adrian.
我想我们有大麻烦了
I think we're in trouble.
我浏览了警察的电话记录  调查泰鲁的活动
I was scanning police calls, following Theroux's movements.
他当时申请调用军犬来停车现场调查
He was calling for some K9 units to the scene of the pullover.
靠
Fuck.
-他们找到药了吗  -找到了
- They found them? - Yeah.
你们打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
我不知道
I don't know.
当证据对你有利时  反复落实证据就好
When the facts are on your side, you pound the facts.
当证据不对你有利时
When the facts are not on your side...
得了吧
Come on.
你在开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
辩方律师  马上坐下
Counselor, sit down right now.
会轮到你的  请继续  助理检察官
You'll get your turn. Continue, Mr. ASA
我再问一遍  泰鲁警官
Again, Officer Theroux,
你今天早晨是否在
did you conduct a search this morning in an area
丹莱恩高速公路的邻接区域进行了搜查
immediately adjacent to the Dan Ryan Expressway?
-是的  -为什么要搜查呢
- I did. - And what occasioned that search?
因为在前一天晚上  我亲眼看到有个东西
The night before, I witnessed an object being thrown
从嫌疑人车的副驾驶座位上扔了出去
from the passenger side of the suspect's car...
他为什么当天晚上没有搜查呢  法官阁下
Come on! Why did he not search the night before, Your Honor?
这就是胡说八道
This is bullshit!
先生  你立刻给我停止
Sir, you will stop right now
不然我就要判你为藐视法庭  继续提问
or we will discuss contempt charges. Go ahead.
事实上  那是个好问题
Well, that is a good question.
你为什么不在前一天晚上就搜查那个区域呢
Why didn't you search the area the night before?
我搜了  但那有茂密的灌木丛还有一个水沟
I did. But there's thick brush there and a gully.
我不可能找到的
I couldn't find anything.
所以我今天早上带着军犬重回那
So I went back with a K9 unit this morning...
引用这种记忆还真是方便
Talk about a convenient memory.
女士  停
Ma'am. No.
谢谢  法官阁下
Thank you, Your Honor.
请你告诉我们
Please, tell the court what,
-你找到了什么东西  -一个白色的塑料袋
- if anything, you found. - A white plastic bag
装有约1.5克的合成性卡西酮类药物
containing approximately 1.5 grams of a synthetic cathinone
-就是常说的毒品浴盐  -没有其它问题了
- commonly known as bath salts. - Nothing further.
他们为什么不把仪表盘的摄像头作为证据呢
Why aren't they introducing the dashboard cam into evidence?
博斯曼先生和洛哈特女士
Mr. Boseman, Ms. Lockhart,
你们俩还需要继续捶桌子吗
are you both done pounding your table?
我道歉  法官阁下
I apologize, Your Honor.
但基于警官新证词的重要性
But given the significance of the officer's new testimony,
我很好奇为什么没有看到
I'm curious why we're not seeing
事发时他仪表盘所录下的视频
his dashboard video of the encounter.
好问题  助理检察官
Good question. Mr. ASA?
法官阁下  视频中不包含任何无罪证据
Your Honor, there's nothing exculpatory on that recording.
好吧  这我就放心了  法官阁下
Oh, well, that's a relief, Your Honor.
我猜你还是想要看看这段视频吧
My guess is you would like to see it.
如果不是太麻烦的话
If it's not too much trouble.
控方有三个小时时间
The State has three hours
-给辩方提供仪表盘所录视频  -休庭
- to provide Defense with the dashboard video. - Adjourned.
想租车的话  得跟服务处预约
Hey, you want a rental, you got to talk to the office.
我不租车  想打听个名字
No, I need a name.
昨天晚上  你开车送的某个客人
Uh, last night, you drove someone.
西装男
A man in a suit.
这个人
This man.
-他做什么了  -没什么
- What'd he do? - Nothing.
他是一场车祸的目击证人
He's a witness to a car accident.
-理查德·赫斯  -他当时要去哪
- Richard Hess. - Where was he headed?
阿灵顿山庄的什么派对
Some party in Arlington Heights.
你好吗  小理
How are you, Rich?
我们认识吗
Do I know you?
我们没有正式见过
Uh, I don't think we've officially met,
但我知道你认识科林·斯威尼
but I know you know Colin Sweeney,
而且我想他可能需要你去为他出庭作证
and I think he may need you to testify on his behalf.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
得了吧  兄弟  他领你去参加了
Come on, man. He was leading you
阿灵顿山庄的派对  药爱派对
to a party in Arlington Heights... the chemsex party...
但他的车被截停了
but his car got pulled over.
仪表盘的摄像头录下了你
This is you on the dashboard videotape.
你停下来等了他们几分钟
You waited a few minutes for them,
但之后你就让司机开车走了
but then told the driver to keep going.
既然你明显已经蠢到家了
Since you're obviously a little dense,
那我就简单点来告诉你
let me dumb it down for you.
滚开
Fuck off.
这家伙绝对看到了什么  但他不肯作证
This guy definitely saw something, but he won't testify.
-我们可以收买他吗  -斯威尼先生
- Can we pay him? - Mr. Sweeney.
假设来说
Hypothetically.
我们可以把他看做一位敌意证人
We can treat him as a hostile witness.
-他为什么不肯作证  -他不想让大家知道
- Why won't he testify? - He doesn't want it to come out
他曾去过哪里
that he was going where he was going.
-哪里  -斯威尼先生要去的那个性爱派对
- And where was that? - The sex party Mr. Sweeney was going to.
他叫什么
What's his name?
理查德·赫斯  怎么  你认识他吗
Richard Hess. Why? You know him?
不认识  你们不能让他出庭作证
No. You will not put him on the stand.
你们无权这么做
You have no right!
你在说什么  他看到了所发生的事
What are you talking about? He saw what happened.
那可不一定
You don't know that.
我坚决要求你们不再联系他
I insist that you not contact him again,
不然我就另找其他的律师
or I'm hiring other lawyers.
-所以你确实打了那个警察  -没有
- So you did beat up that cop? - No.
什么  没有
What? No.
那为什么你不希望我们联系他
Why don't you want us to get this guy?
因为我不需要理由
Because I don't need a reason.
我在你办公室等你  戴安
I'll be in your office, Diane.
我想我明白了
I think I understand.
什么  我不明白
What? I don't.
理查德·赫斯是佛罗里达州的地产大亨
Richard Hess is a Florida real estate billionaire
他被派到芝加哥来审查
who's been sent to Chicago to vet...
大使人选
ambassadors.
别那么看我
Don't act like that.
如果你不能买标价出售的东西
What's the point of being rich
那成为有钱人还有什么意思
if you can't buy what's for sale?
一个大使的职位
An ambassadorship?
我给他的政治行动委员会资助了一百多万美元
I gave over a million dollars to his campaign PAC.
会员是有特权的
Membership has its privileges.
所以施展你们的魔法  让这些控告消失吧
So work your magic and make these charges go away.
我必须看起来身家清白
I need to look clean.
那就让赫斯来为你出庭作证
Then get Hess to testify on your behalf.
泰鲁的毒品证词对你很不利
This drug testimony from Theroux hurts you.
不行  想其它的办法
No. Find another way.
警察暴力执法案件是你们的专长
Police brutality is your specialty,
而我就是一个货真价实的受害者
and I'm a bona fide victim here!
并不是只有黑人才会被暴力执法的
It's not just the black people who get brutalized.
还有我这样的人  被误解的人
It's people like me... the misunderstood.
白人亿万富翁  众人宣称的杀妻犯
The white billionaire wife-killer, allegedly.
我的神啊
Oh, God.
玛娅
Maia.
她在试图暗示你知晓庞氏骗局
She's trying to suggest you knew about the Ponzi Scheme,
所以你才没有让艾米的父母加入基金
and that's why you waived Amy's parents off.
-我明白  -你真知道吗
- Yeah. I know. - Did you?
当然不知道
No.
但你听起来可并不确定
You don't sound definite.
你有告诉他我爸爸的退休账户里有11万美元
Did you tell him my father's IRA comes to $110,000,
而且还有三万美元国债了吗
that he's got another $30,000 in T-Bills?
我不知道  我
I don't know. I...
你不知道你是不是有意不让她父母投资的
You don't know if you waived Amy's parents off?
我知道这很困难
I know this has been hard...
我知道这几个月对你来说很不容易
I know these months have been hard on you, and you feel,
无论对错  你都为你父母的行为而有负罪感
rightly or wrongly, guilty for your parents' actions.
不  这和那些无关
No, that's not what this is.
你自己甚至都不会注意到  玛娅
You don't even need to be conscious of it, Maia.
你的负罪感可能会歪曲你的记忆
Your guilt could just be coloring your memories.
你可能会让自己承担远超于应受的罪责
You could be seeing yourself as more culpable than you are.
这是你的天主教罪恶
It's your Catholic guilt.
天主教罪恶  指天主教教徒或堕落者
他们所供认的远超过他们实际应当承担的罪
你在自我谴责
You are condemning yourself.
在忏悔室里这么做没关系
That's fine for the confessional,
但在这里是要承担后果的
but here, it has real repercussions.
他们可以让你坐牢的
They could put you in jail.
你父亲真的会拒绝14万美金吗
Your father'd really turn down $140,000?
他一向如此
Ah. Well, he does it all the time.
你到底有没有告诉你父亲
Did you really tell your dad?
卢卡  我没告诉我父亲
Lucca, I didn't tell my dad.
没告诉他什么
Didn't tell him what?
我没告诉他艾米的父母想投资
About Amy's parents' investment.
我假装告诉他了  但是  我没告诉
I pretended to, but... I never told him.
你什么意思  我当然告诉我父亲了
What do you mean? Of course I told my dad.
我为什么会不说呢
Why wouldn't I?
好吧  情况不妙
Okay, this isn't good.
你是准备承认你闯了大祸
You're ready to admit you killed Biggie.
我一定是不知道从哪儿得知了庞氏骗局
I must have somehow known about the Ponzi scheme.
不然为什么我没让艾米的父母投资呢
Otherwise, why wouldn't I have let Amy's parents invest?
-这不能说明什么  -能
- That doesn't mean anything. - It does.
卢卡
Lucca.
我早知道
I knew.
问题在于那些毒品
The problem is the drugs.
除此以外的事法官都会听我们讲理
Judge was listening to us on everything else.
问题在于被扔出窗户的毒品
It's the drugs thrown out the freaking window.
所以我们利用赫斯
So we use Hess.
我们说服斯威尼必须利用他的审查者
We convince Sweeney he has to use his vetter.
不  我们得着手于毒品  戴安
No. We need to go at the drugs, Diane.
这也有助于我们应对平民警察问责办公室
That helps us with COPA, too.
他们想开除泰鲁
They want to kick Theroux off the force.
我们只是...
We just...
我们没有给他们足够的理由这么做
We haven't given 'em enough of a reason to do it.
那么我们就陷入僵局了
Then we're stuck.
戴安
Diane?
你在这里过得开心吗
You happy here?
在你的律所吗
What, at your firm?
是的
Yeah.
-开心啊  怎么了  -我不知道
- Yes. Why? - I don't know.
你本想退休的
You wanted to retire.
是啊
Yes.
生活会用它自己的方式告诉你你是谁
Well, life has a way of reminding you of who you are.
我想我不是那种会退休的人
Guess I'm not the retiring type.
你在这里过得开心吗
Are you happy here?
问住你了
Gotcha.
我喜欢...
I like...
打败别人和...
getting the better of people, and...
维持某些东西的生命
keeping something alive.
你知道吗  看着这里的这些员工
You know? Look out there
想着如果我不能让这家律所继续经营
at all those employees, and realizing
他们就可能会失业
they might not have jobs if I don't keep this going.
是的  这感觉很棒
Yeah. That is a good feeling.
好了
Okay.
该回家了
Time to go home.
我们什么时候一起吃个晚饭吧
Let's get dinner sometime.
好吗
Okay?
很好啊
That'd be nice.
是的
Yeah.
非法持有毒品
Possession.
这是非法持有毒品  笨蛋
It was possession! Stupid!
-什么  -我太笨了
- What? - I am so stupid.
它就在我们面前明摆着呢
It was right there in front of our eyes.
-什么明摆着  -他叫什么
- What was? - What is his name?
托德·努特森
Todd Knutsen.
你认识
Are you familiar with
安德鲁·泰鲁警官吗  努特森先生
Officer Andrew Theroux, Mr. Knutsen?
认识  他就是几天前让我靠边停车的人
Oh, yeah. He's the one that pulled me over a few nights ago.
你能在法庭上讲讲当时发生了什么吗
Would you tell the court what happened?
我正从我母亲的住处开车回家
I was driving home from my mom's house.
他让我靠边停车  说我变换车道前
He pulled me over, said I was switching lanes
没有发信号  我发了信号的
without signaling. I wasn't.
他让我下车  这样他就能搜查我的车
He asked me to step out of the car so he could search it.
然后他用手铐拷住我
Then he handcuffs me and says
说我因持有海洛因被捕了
I'm under arrest for possession of heroin.
你持有海洛因吗
Were you in possession of heroin?
没有  是他放进我车里的
No, he planted it.
事实上  指控最终不是被撤销了吗
In fact, weren't the charges eventually dropped?
是的  今天撤销的
Yeah, just today.
其他的警察说他经常做这种事
The other cops say this happens a lot with him.
反对  法官阁下...
Objection, Your Honor...
反对有效  不过你可能要
Yes, sustained. But you might want to
重新考虑这次起诉了  助理检察官先生
reconsider your charge here, Mr. ASA.
没有其他问题了  法官阁下  谢谢
Nothing further, your Honor. Thank you.
-麦克格拉斯先生  -没有问题了
- Mr. McGrath? - Nothing further.
证人可以离开了
The witness is dismissed.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢
Thanks.
真的没必要这么做
That's really not necessary.
这不是什么大事
It's no big deal.
这是证券交易委员会审查  当然是大事
It's a SEC audit. Of course it's a big deal.
-算了吧 贾克斯  -你们俩能安静点吗
- Come on. Jax. - Would you two be quiet?
亲爱的
Hey, hon.
我们很快就会出来
We'll be right out.
我觉得我们不应该
I don't think we should
把你父母的钱和我父母的钱混在一起
entangle your parents' money with my parents'.
基金出了什么问题吗
Is there something wrong with the fund?
你还好吗
Are you good?
我不知道
I don't know.
听着  玛娅
Listen, Maia,
我能想到很多原因解释
I can think of a dozen reasons
你为什么不让艾米的父母投资
why you didn't let Amy's parents invest.
首先  你不想把金钱和爱情混为一谈
First and foremost, you didn't want to mix up finances with love.
我觉得这很有道理
That makes complete sense to me.
你这么认为吗
You think so?
是的
Yeah, I do.
这次你准备好了吗
You ready again?
最后一次看牙医
Last dentist visit.
J.K.
代表"只是开玩笑的"
That's "Just kidding."
小孩子们都这么说
It's what the kids say.
感谢你的帮忙
I wanted to thank you for you help.
不用客气
You're welcome.
我还希望你明白
And I wanted to let you know
好人没好报
that no good deed goes unpunished.
大约一小时前  某个亿万富翁被任命为
About an hour ago, some billionaire was named
下一任驻德国大使了
the next ambassador to Germany.
我输了
I lost it.
听到这个消息我很遗憾
I'm sorry to hear that.
我简直不敢相信我浪费了四个月学德语
I can't believe I wasted four months trying to learn German.
我  不
Ich. Nicht.
我相信你会撑过去的
Well, I'm sure you'll survive.
而且  你也不用涉身我们对库克县的诉讼了
Also, it'll free you up for our lawsuit against Cook County.
泰鲁已经被开除了
Theroux's been kicked off the force,
但我们正在准备一个600万美元的民事诉讼案
but we've got a six million dollar civil suit in the works.
不  我不会那么做的
Uh, no, I'm not doing that.
你会的
Uh, yes, you are.
不  抱歉
No. Sorry.
我正努力竞选驻梵蒂冈大使
I'm trying for Ambassador to the Vatican.
再次感谢
Again, thanks.
我会再来拜访的
I'll drop by again.
你准备好结束这事了吗  玛娅
Are you ready to finish this up, Maia?
她准备好了
She is.
你问我为什么我不让艾米的父母向基金投资
You asked me why I didn't want Amy's parents to invest in the fund.
事实是  把家庭和金钱混为一谈
And the truth is, it just seemed like a bad idea
不是个好主意
to mix family and finances.
据我的经验  玛娅
In my experience, Maia,
当一个人说"事实是"的时候
whenever somebody says, "The truth is,"
往往意味着他说的不是事实
that usually means it's not.
-不是这样的  -我很喜欢你  玛娅
- That's not... - I like you, Maia.
我觉得你很聪明  又有洞察力
I think you're smart, I think you're perceptive,
但我认为你犯罪了
and I think you committed a crime here.
我认为你知道你父母的庞氏骗局
I think you knew about your parents' Ponzi scheme,
我将向联邦检察官办公室
and I'm going to recommend
提议起诉你
prosecution by the U.S. Attorney's Office.
-这是供证协议环节  -是  但她说谎了
- This was a proffer session! - Yes, but she lied.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.